Alberto Arriaga Felix

Cell: (818) 219-4323 albertoarriagafelix@gmail.com

Web: AFelix.tech

linkedin.com/in/alberto-arriaga-felix my.indeed.com/p/albertoa-5x7ztov

ABOUT ME

I have a passion for work in electronics and my current goal is to advance my knowledge in the field by working on interesting projects. I've worked and studied extensively in both electronic design and computer programming. I have earned a Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering from the University of California Riverside, with a specialization on embedded systems, and Associates Degrees in Computer Science and Mathematics.

My specialties are:

- Information Technology, Computer and Electronics Repair
- Embedded Systems, and other small form systems like Raspberry Pi and Arduino like devices.
- Low level programming, using FPGAs with VHDL or Verilog, and understanding of semiconductor layout design.

General Skills

- -Languages: English and Spanish.
- -Worked with multidisciplinary teams while taking leadership on technical tasks, and completed various Computer Science and Electrical Engineering projects.
- -Proficient if working by myself, can organize tasks logically and efficiently, and write about them clearly in technical reports.
- -Experience in finding solutions to technical tasks using computers/electronics.
- -Strong analytical skills, math & science background, and hardware repair background from previous jobs.
- -Fast learner, and always looking to learn something new.

Specific Skills

Software MATLAB, MathWorks Simulink, PSpice, Visual Studio, Atmel Studio, Xilinx Vivado, Synopsys Design. C (for Arduino and AVR), C++, Java, Python (for Raspberry Pi), VHDL (for FPGA), Verilog (for Synopsys). **Programming**

Atmel AVR Microcontrollers, Arduino, Basys FPGA, or Raspberry Pi. Hardware

Computer Skills Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Adobe Photoshop.

OS + Web Windows OS (XP,7,8,10) and Linux (Ubuntu, Raspbian). HTML+CSS, JavaScript.

EDUCATION

September 2014 University of California, Riverside Riverside, CA

- June 2017 **Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering**

Study Focus: Embedded Systems and VLSI, Nanotechnology and Semiconductor Materials.

Link: www.ee.ucr.edu/academics/undergraduate-program

2009-13 Los Angeles Mission College and Valley College

Associate in Arts - Computer Science June 2013

Sylmar and Valley Glen, CA

North Hollywood, CA 91606

Associate in Arts - Mathematics

Certificate in Microcomputer Programming August 2013

Certificate in Microcomputer Applications Management

Link: lamission.edu/Computer-Science/Certificates-and-Degrees.aspx

lamission.edu/Mathematics-Department/Degree-Reequirements.aspx

WORK HISTORY

October 2018 -	IT Consulting/Web Developer at Self Startup	Corona, CA
	Designed and implemented online commerce websites. Set up office computers, tech	

equipment, and point of sale technology.

Electrical Engineer at Self Employed/University of California, Riverside 2014-17 Riverside, CA

> Designed and build custom electronics using Raspberry Pi, FPGA, Arduino and Atmel AVR embedded. Applied knowledge of analog and digital signal processing, analog to digital conversion, power systems, computer vision, control theory, and semiconductor processing. Programming skills used, MATHLAB, Python, C, C++,

Verilog, and VHDL. Designed and manufactured PCB boards.

Information Technology Specialist at LA Mission College North Hollywood, CA 2012-14

> Developed applications for JAVA and C++ based systems. Used Visual Studio platform. Applied knowledge of Information Technology. Volunteered in Computer and Electronics Repair. Build new computers and electronics to the specifications and needs of customers. Added computer software/hardware to existing computers and solved technical tasks for customers.